Yes! I'll keep you hooked on Ikirin World whether you're asleep or awake!
This is Kashiyuki, a.k.a. Yukirii!
Today! Makeup everyday!
So, I'd like to show you all my recent makeup.
I'd like you all to take a look at my latest makeup!
I've been wearing no makeup today as usual.
I just did a little skin care.
I have some acne scars and pimples again.
Well, don't worry about it, just hide it.
I'm going to do it right away.
First of all, I'd like to get rid of some redness.
This is Givenchy's Prismatic Libre Skin Care Ring Collector.
Long name
Green.
Oh, I have to pin my bangs.
Today
I'm going to clip it with a tabe-ko animal.
For example, I'd like to pin my bangs on the redness here and there.
I'm going to apply it directly to the redness on the sides of the nose and acne scars.
I'm going to apply it directly.
Like this
Awww!
Use a sponge like this.
First, I use green to reduce the redness like this.
And then
I'm always using a primer because I'm worried about the pores on my nose.
But today, I'm going to use a normal primer.
I'm sorry.
The cap is gone.
RMK's Makeup Base Limited Edition Peach Pearl.
This is it.
Take it off.
Go, go, go, go!
Isn't this amazing?
It gives a nice glow and tone up.
I've already done my nose with it today.
I didn't apply a lot of primer.
I didn't need to apply a lot of primer.
The technique she taught me is really amazing.
It's really amazing!
I'm using it as soon as I can.
Here's the base coat.
Then I'm going to apply foundation.
Today, I'm going to use this one.
J&b's cushion foundation in light beige.
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to put a little water on the sponge.
I only need a little bit more than you think.
This is what I'm going to put on the sponge.
I'm going to put it on.
I was already doing the overwhelmingly thick coverage or something like that.
I've been doing this for a long time.
But if I use concealer after this, I found that it works surprisingly well.
I've learned that it's surprisingly good if you cover it up well with concealer.
It looks a little yellowish here.
I'm sorry.
It might be hard to tell.
It's much lighter.
But... the primer I used earlier did a pretty good job.
It's doing a great job.
I'm going to apply it on the sponge with water.
I'm going to apply it.
Like this.
There's still a lot of this stuff left.
I'm usually so worried about this kind of stuff.
Not yet.
You're not even close to me.
There's still a little bit of pore on my nose.
To be honest, if it were me, I'd be more concerned.
In order to keep it from falling apart.
I'm going to use this foundation here.
I'm going to apply it thinly while adhering to the skin.
I've never touched it like this before.
I used to apply it so thickly
I used to put on so much foundation
But now it's so thin that it still looks like bare skin.
I'm going to stop once it's still there.
I'm going to stop now.
And the most important thing is concealer.
This is Luna Concealer.
I put it on my hand and take it off with a brush.I put it on my hand and take it from here with a brush.
A little bit at a time, really.
A little bit at a time, and then a little bit at a time.
I'm going to start with this, like this, like this.
I spread it out very carefully, very carefully.
If you touch it, you can feel it sagging.
The amount.
The amount is like painting a thin picture.
Keep going and going and going.
Carefully, carefully, carefully.
And here, too.
Little by little, like this.
You may think, "I can't take this much time.
To be honest, you may think, "I can't take this much time.
But it's really, really, really hard to make it fall apart.
It lasts longer than you'd think.
Also, I'd like to know about this nose.
I want you to teach me how to fill in these pores with this concealer.
I just fill in the pores with this concealer and make them disappear.
It disappears quite well.
Maybe I've been applying too much foundation.
To be honest...
But, you know...
It's a little different when I'm at a concert or on TV.
It's a little different.
But when I put it on like this
Surprisingly, the pores on my nose
It's a strange thing that pores on the nose become less noticeable
How's this?
How is it? I don't think it looks thicker than usual.
There's still a little bit.
But honestly, I don't look at people's faces this closely.
This is about right, right?
Yes, it is.
It's totally different.
It's like a bare skin.
I'm done.
So, I recently discovered, or rather, invented...
Oh, this.
Addiction's Skin Reflect Fresh Concealer No. 001.
I put this bright color right here.
In the triangle.
Then I feel like my nose looks more prominent.
I don't know why.
I feel like it's going in a little bit here.
I feel like it looks a little bit tighter.
Now, I'm going to lighten the edges of these lips with a brighter color.
It looks good, doesn't it?
The base is done!
And here we go.
Innisfree's Noce Balm Mineral Powder N.
Put this on your forehead.
I think I'm going to use this today.
I think I'll use this today... for the powder.
I'm not going to be doing live shows or anything today, I'm going to be doing my makeup every day.
RMK's Silk Fit Setting Powder
I'm going to use this.
Softly all over the face.
Lightly, lightly, lightly...
Yes!
Base is done!
Can you tell? A little more than usual.
It doesn't hide the dark circles...
But that's okay.
Okay! Let's go to the eyeshadows!
I've already shown you this one before.
I think I'll go with this one. Let's do it again.
Dageek's No. 4 Pastel Dream.
This is my favorite.
Use the Ansi brush.
This color here.
I use a little bit of this color here and a little bit of this color here.
First of all, I do what you taught me to do.
Create a base for the whole eye like this.
Top and bottom.
I've never done anything like this before.
When I do this, it doesn't look like I'm applying eyeshadow at all.
It doesn't suddenly feel like I'm applying eye shadow to my eyes.
It's very thin, really.
It's more like a foundation for the whole eye.
This is about the same level as the eyes.This is about the size of the eye.
I was taught to do it like this.
I put a little bit of color on it.
And this...
Ta-da!
I'm going to use You Pink.
I took this color of this pink
I put a little bit of this color.
I'm just going to put a little bit of shadow on the upper eyelid.
I'm just going to do a little bit of shading on the upper lids.
Today, I'm going to do a little bit of the lower part of the eyelid.
It's really pretty! I love the color!
You can get a nice shade like this.
But I think it makes the eyes stand out a little bit more.
I think it makes the eyes stand out a little more.
Okay!
And then...
Let's put the lame on the eyelid first.
I'm going to take this lame and I'm going to put it on my finger.
Where should I put it today?
Let's put it in the top middle.
This is the one that's easy to use for everyday.
It's not too much glittery lame.
It gives a little bit of luster to the eyelid.
I'm OK with it, I think it gives a little bit of shine.
Then I think I'll paint the tips of my eyebrows.
There you go!
Elegance Eyebrow Slim
I'm familiar with this brush.
I'm going to use this brush.
It's a new brush, so it's beautiful.
Shape it up.
Today, I'm going to do the eyebrows.
I don't want to make it look like it's not there.
I'm going to use this pencil.
I'm going to start with the missing part.
I'm going to use this pencil to define the bottom line of my eyebrows.
I have a lot of eyebrows.
I don't draw my eyebrows that hard.
I draw it a little softly.
As much as possible, I try not to show the line.
I added a little more on top.
This is the base of my eyebrows.
And then
This brush is used to make the eyebrows thick like this, and then this brush...
This is the brush to make the eyebrows thick.
Then, paint the eyebrows with this brush.
That's it! CAMMAKE's
Mixed Eyebrow Color C01
It's pink. This one of this.
I took the top two colors and the lighter two colors
and put them on.
from this area as well.
The inner part is already soft and fluffy.
The beginning of the brow.
A little bit at a time so that the beginning of the eyebrows are soft and fluffy.
Apply a little bit at a time so that the beginning of the eyebrows are soft and fluffy.
I'm addicted to making them a little fluffy and fuzzy.
I'm addicted to it.
How is it?
The right side is a little high.
My left side is a little lower.
My eyebrows are a little lower.
It's like a slight skeletal adjustment.
I'm going to add where it's missing.
And then, I'm going to add a darker color.
I'm going to add a little bit of darker color to the bottom part of my eyebrows.
I'm going to add a little bit to the lighter areas here.
The beginning of this area is a little bit like this.
It doesn't look like a line.
Also, the thicker the brush, the easier it is to fluff it up.
Okay.
And the eyebrow mascara and Y are both pink.
I really like pink today too!
CAMMAKE Smart Mini Brow Color
N01
Somehow this one too
Soft and long hairs
Oh, that's nice.
This is how it's done.
Now let's do some lashes.Okay, I'm going to do some lashes.
I'm perming my lashes right now.
The top is just the bottom.
I'm going to lower them.
That's scary!
Lower them.
I haven't drawn eyeliner, let's draw eyeliner.
Cammake creamy touch liner.
No. 07. It's a kind of azuki-bean color.
Here.
I'm going to draw it on.
I think I drew a little too much on top.
This eyeliner is like this.
I used the image of casually pushing in the eyeliner.
Okay!
I drew eyeliner!
And then...
Gosh, my stomach is growling.
Let's paint the lower eyelid.
On the lower eyelid.
Use this fine brush.
Use this brush.
We're going to lower the center of gravity.
First of all, this color of Bageek.
I used to put it in very thin.
Now I'm going to apply it boldly and widely.
From here, we're going to move it down.
The entire lower eyelid will look pinkish.
I also like to brighten up the tear ducts.
I like to brighten up the tear ducts, but first I use this pink to lower the color.
This is cute.
I'm going to work the pink into the lower eyelid.
And here's the You Pink.
How much do you love pink? It's like, "How much do you love pink?
Take this shade of You Pink.
I apply it widely on the lower eyelid in this triangular zone.
It's not too sheer, or it doesn't come out too fast, so you can adjust the amount.
You can adjust the amount.
So it's your preference.
Okay, about this much.
You can gradually create a shadow.
And then take the darker color here.
And then I'm going to tighten it up further down here.
Darker! Like this.
And then use this darker color to tighten the top as well.
Like tracing over the eyeliner and eyeshadow.
The border between the eyeliner and the eyeshadow should not be too obvious.
Blend the eyeliner with the eyeliner.
Like this.
Then apply mascara.
Etcuse Eye Edition Mascara Base
Like I was taught this.
I think the length here is a bit conspicuous anyway.
Anyway, I'm just going to spread it out horizontally.
And how to apply these lashes.
I learned this.
I'm going to paint outward.
I didn't know that.
I've been doing it up and up and up.
Like this.
Paint horizontally outward like this
I'm going to paint like this
Oh, wow.
I've never applied mascara like this before.
And when I apply it horizontally and sideways, I feel like it makes my lashes look clumpy.
Like this.
If you apply it outwards and outwards, it looks like a bunch of lashes.
I should apply the lower lashes too.
Déjà vu, Lash Up.
I'm going to apply it with this thin, thin brush.
First of all, this edge, the top edge, anyway, a little bit thicker.
And then, just like this...
It looks like this.
It's done!
And now, the usual
Here comes the nose!
I'm going to start with the one I'm going to shave first, today.
I learned this one too.
Professionals are amazing, aren't they?
This nose is so shiny.
So I'm going to use this smooth powder.This silky powder and
Shading are mixed together
I use it in the Lilimu.
I put the powder on this brush like this
I make it smooth and then I put it on this brush like this.
I use this brush to mix it with this gray powder
And take it.
Sharpen the tip of the brush
Make a V shape.
And a little bit here.
And down here, too, to make it shorter.
And then we're going to shave it down the middle, and then we're going to shave it down the middle.
There's a lot more to makeup that you don't know about.
And also, I'm going to shave the nose a little bit like this.
I'm going to make the edge of the nose a little bit tighter.
I'm going to smash it vertically here.
And then I'm going to take this area here.
So that it doesn't go here.
Smooth it over here.
It's going to look like a great nose shadow.
Avoid the inside as much as possible.
Avoid here.
Let it go like this over here.
I'm going to create a natural shadow.
It looks so natural.
I've only done this one.
This is by far the most indented area.
It's really amazing!
Thanks a lot for the nose shadow.
I'm going to hold the mirror away from me a little bit.
And see if it's natural or not.
Good.
And then
I'm going to put a highlight.
Highlight.
Right this way.
This is my favorite.
Ta-da!
Lior's Backstage Face Glow Palette.
It's number 4, rose gold.
I use a little bit of this color here and a little bit of this color here with this thin brush.
On the nose, at the tip of the nose, where you want it to be the highest.
This is the shine.
Excuse me for the close-up.
The tip of the nose should be glossy to make the nose look glossy.
This is the gloss.
And then I'm going to use this color here, and I'm going to put it in vertically, softly.
Oh!
Now the nose is done, and it looks shiny.
And then highlight with a little brush like this.
I want this glow here.
After applying skin care cream or milky lotion...
After applying emulsion or cream, there is a place where the light comes in.
You can put it in this kind of scene.
Put the color with the most glitter on the top of the eyes.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is the same kind of shine as when someone else took a picture of me.
You said you had it taken by someone else.
When you take a picture, when you get a picture...
The sparkle will show up in the picture.
It's nice.
And the blush.
Take the u-pink blush and put it on the sponge.
I'm going to put it from here to the side like this.
So cute!
I'm so good at makeup now!
I know it's a little late for this, but
I haven't done shading yet.
I'm almost done!
Shading.
I'm going to do a little more over this screen.
Click, click, click, click.
Tut-tut-tut.
And a little bit of the top, just a little bit of the top, just a little bit of the top
And I'll add just a little bit of mascara on top.
That's what I'm going to do today.
Kingdom's curling mascara.
This is the one that gives a little bit of a bunchy look.
Side to side, side to side.
Go on.Get in.
Let's try Hot Bureaus!
While the hot mouser is warming up
Apply lipstick
High lip
make up every day
And what should I do with
What should I do with my lips?
I think I'll go with Lip Monster today.
Rustic number seven.
I'll do more than time
And the top one, I'm going to go with a feeling
I'm going to go louder than a sound mouthful.
Lately, I've been loving glosses.
Peripera's number 3.
Ink-glistening lip gloss.
It's like an indescribable rose brown
This is so shiny.
Look at all these people.
It's like a rose brown, and this one's shiny.
Just look at it, guys.
This is so
And let the bottom lashes fall down properly.
Okay! Done!
It's done!
The key is to make the makeup look shiny and sideways, and to make it look sideways.
Also, the way the foundation is applied, and the concealer, it really doesn't look thick, and it keeps its shape even after a long time.
When you apply it that way, it keeps its shape even after a long time. This is how I do my makeup every day these days.
Recently, I've been doing a lot of makeup for TV and live performances in my videos.
I haven't been doing my daily makeup much, so this is how I've been doing it lately.
I hope you will find it useful as well!
That's all for now! This is Yukirinu here with Yukirinu!
See you soon! Bye!